Does it look okay?
大丈夫そうですか?
Oh, okay, okay.
あっ、 オ ッケーオッケー
Hello.
こんにちは
Why are you smiling like that?
なんでそんな笑ってんの?
No, it's so surreal.
いや、あの、すごいシュールだなっていう
Oh, surreal?
あ、シュール?
It's a picture, sorry.
絵図じゃんか、すみません
You were talking about my side, right?
俺の副面のこと言ったやろ、それ
So, uh, I was taking pictures last time.
じゃ、あの、前回は撮ってたんですけど、
Um, apart from the cameraman,
あの、カメラマンさんと別にいると、
I'm sorry I laughed because it was so surreal.
すごくシュールで笑っちゃってごめんね
It's different again.
また違うよね
surely.
確かに
Last time it was 1.
前回1回1だったもんね
That's right.
そうなんですよ
Last time I said it, I got a different impression.
前回言ったらなんか印象違うね
Maybe it's because the clothes are different.
服が違うからかな
Well, maybe.
そうですね、多分
Yeah, I feel like an idol today.
うん、 なんか今日はアイドルっぽい
Didn't you say something last time?
前回もなんか言ってませんでしたっけ?
Last time, I felt like one of them was kind of feminine.
前回どっちかとなんか女子やなっぽい感じだったよね
What do you think, since then?
どうですか、あれから?
Is it from then?
あれからですか
You said you didn't have a boyfriend.
彼氏いないって言ってたけど
Ah, but I found someone who is interested.
あ、でも、気になる人はできました
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
What about your boyfriend?
彼氏は?
Not?
じゃなくて?
I already have someone I'm interested in, not just a boyfriend.
彼氏じゃなくて、気になる人はもうできました
Eh, what kind of person is he?
えっ、どんな人?
What kind of person are you?
どんな人?
woman
女性
I was curious about it while I was on LINE for a while.
は ちょっとLINEしてるうちに気になっちゃって
It's someone I'm not dating.
付き合いしてない人なんだ
I agree.
そうですね
it is?
それは?
Did you have sex?
エッチしたの?
I haven't done it yet, obviously.
まだしてないです、さすがに
Seriously?
マジで?
We're not dating anymore, yet.
もう付き合いしてないんだよ、まだ
Seriously?
マジで?
Well, the person you like isn't me, is it?
そのさ、好きな人ってさ、俺のことじゃない?
I just don't understand.
ちょっとわかんない
I guess I don't understand what you mean.
ちょっと言った意味がわからないんかな
No?
違うん?
That's not true.
違いますよ
Seriously?
マジかよ
I like it.
俺は好きだよ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Is it okay if we are dating?
付き合いしてるけどいいの?
yeah?
ん?
Huh?
えっ?
We're dating though.
付き合いしてるけど
付 き合いしてるけど
Yeah.
うん
With
付
We are together.
き 合いしてる
difficult.
難しい
Yeah, we're not talking here.
うん、ここに話し合いない
I'm in great spirits.
すごい気合いしてる
Yeah.
うん
Keke reflects that.
ケケが反映してる
Yeah.
うん
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Show me your bunts.
ちょっとバンツ見せて
Buntz?
バンツ?
yeah?
ん?
Yeah.
うん
Just show me a little bit.
ちょっとだけ見せて
Are you not dating?
付き合いしてない?
Yeah.
うん
Are you not dating?
付き合いしてない?
Yeah.
うん
Yeah, we're not dating.
うん、付き合いしてない
Shall we open it?
開いちゃうか
It'll open.
開いちゃう
Open it and spread it out.
開 いて広げてごらん
Show me the cat.
ネコ見せて
It's beautiful, that.
綺麗だよ、それ
difficult.
難しい
Spread it out properly, yourself.
ちゃんと広げて、自分
Look.
ほ ら
difficult.
難しい
Did you do this?
こんなことしてた?
There isn't.
ないよ
Oh, that's amazing.
ああ、すごい
Looks good.
よく見える
Hurry up and give it here.
急いでいらっしゃいで、さあ、ここにあげて
What do you think?
どう だ?
You look like you're going to sleep, give it to me.
寝ようだね、ちょうだい
yeah?
ん?
ah.
ああ
Somehow, I haven't slept.
なんか、寝てない
yeah?
ん?
It's wet.
ぬぐれてる
It was wiped clean.
ぬぐれてた
Was it wiped?
ぬぐれてた?
Yeah.
うん
Don't do it.
しないで
し ない で
Yeah.
うん
what?
なに?
Move your hips.
腰動かして
Yeah.
うん
Sit down.
腰をつけて
It was wiped clean.
ぬぐれてた
Why don't you come here?
ここにこいってごらん?
Yeah.
うん